{
    "subject": "resource/Sovereign_Military_Order_of_Malta",
    "predicate": "ontology/currency",
    "object": "resource/Maltese_scudo",
    "human_readable": "The currency of the Sovereign Military Order of Malta is Maltese scudo.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9553488492965698,
            "question": "What is the currency of the Sovereign Military Order of Malta?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7517104744911194,
            "question": "Is 'Maltese scudo' a real currency?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6960000991821289,
            "question": "What is the name of the Maltese currency?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6000385284423828,
            "question": "To which organization does the Maltese scudo belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5295854210853577,
            "question": "What is the history of the Maltese scudo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38650617003440857,
            "question": "Are there any unique features of the Maltese scudo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36255866289138794,
            "question": "What are some challenges faced by the Maltese scudo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28679877519607544,
            "question": "How is the Maltese scudo used in daily transactions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11878731101751328,
            "question": "What are some other currencies used in Europe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.07037575542926788,
            "question": "Can you name any other currencies with a historical connection to a specific organization?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The currency of the Sovereign Military Order of Malta is Maltese scudo.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9077_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some other currencies used in Europe?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9077_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is the Maltese scudo used in daily transactions?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9077_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some challenges faced by the Maltese scudo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9077_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9077_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9077_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9077_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9077_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9077_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9077_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9077_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9077_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9077_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9077_70.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The documents mention that the official currency of the Sovereign Military Order of Malta is indeed the Maltese Scudo, and it is subdivided into various sub-units such as tar\u00ec, grani, and piccioli."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"The official currency of the Sovereign Military Order of Malta, which retains its claims of sovereignty under international law and has been granted permanent observer status at the United Nations, is the Maltese scudo,\" supporting the given statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}